coalitionforcollegeaccess.org 2018-12-25

# Coalition for College

This privacy policy applies to (i) information collected by www.coalitionforcollege.org, the web site of The Coalition for College, as well as (ii) information that the Coalition receives through www.mycoalition.org.

Specifically, this policy will notify you of the following:

  * What personal information is collected from you through www.coalitionforcollege.org, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  * Your access to and control over the information you provide through www.coalitionforcollege.org.
  * What personal information we receive from www.mycoalition.org, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  * The security measures used by the Coalition to protect your information.
  * The Coalition’s privacy policy does not apply when you interact with links to otherwebsites. 

## Information Collection, Use, and Sharing 

The Coalition collects information that you voluntarily provide through www.mycoalition.org via emails to info@coalitionapp.org or through forms hosted on the web site. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use this information to respond to you regarding the reason(s) you contacted us. We will not share this information with any third party outside of our organization other than as necessary to fulfill your request or answer your question.

## Your Access to and Control Over Information 

You may contact the Coalition via the email at info@coalitionapp.org to request any of the following: (i) access to personal information you have previously provided through emails to @coalitionapp.org or forms hosted on www.coalitionforcollege.org, if any; (ii) changes or corrections to any such information; (iii) deletion of any such information; and/or (iv) a response to any concern(s) you have about our use of your information.

## INFORMATION RECEIVED FROM WWW.MYCOALITION.ORG

The platform described on www.coalitionforcollegea.org and offered through www.mycoalition.org is provided by the Coalition's third party technology service provider, CollegeNET. Please be aware that with respect to www.mycoalition.org, the Coalition is not responsible for any privacy or security practices, and that CollegeNET’s privacy and security policies exclusively apply. You may access these CollegeNET policies at: [corp.collegenet.com/privacy.html](https://corp.collegenet.com/privacy.html).

CollegeNET may provide the Coalition with aggregated and de-identified metrics and other data regarding www.mycoalition.org users and/or services. CollegeNET may also provide the Coalition with certain information that platform users provide in the “Profile Section” of their platform accounts on www.mycoalition.org, including name, date of birth, mailing address, email address, phone number(s), sex and gender, race/ethnicity, current schooling status, high school information, grade level, year of planned college enrollment, academic interests, language proficiencies, parent/guardian education level, fee waiver qualification, and application status. The Coalition will not sell or rent this data or information to anyone. Rather, this data and information will be used by the Coalition solely to (i) provide platform users with additional information regarding the Coalition’s free college planning tools, the application, and My Coalition Counselor resources and (ii) assess and improve upon the Coalition’s activities and efforts in support of its mission to increase student access to information about colleges and improve the college application process. Please note that we cannot change information you provide through www.mycoalition.org. If you want to update such information, you must go through the www.mycoalition.org website and make such requests in accordance with CollegeNET policies.

## Security

We take commercially reasonable measures to protect the information you provide on www.coalitionforcollege.org and that we otherwise receive from CollegeNET through www.mycoalition.org. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any or all of the information you transmit to www.coalitionforcollege.org and/or www.mycoalition.org, and you do so at your own risk.

## Other Websites

This web site contains links to sites other than www.mycoalition.org. Please be aware that the Coalition is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other sites. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personal information.

## Minors

The Coalition does not intend to collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under 13 years old, you should not provide personal information to the Coalition.

## Updates

Our privacy policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

If you have questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [info@coalitionapp.org](mailto:info@coalitionapp.org?subject=Questions%20about%20the%20Coalition%27s%20Privacy%20Policy).
